<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TextAdventure-Android</string>

    <string name="End_Story">Your journey has ended for now. The game has been reset and is ready for you to try again when you are ready.</string>
    <string name="End_Ans1"></string> // both buttons are hidden
    <string name="End_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="Temp_Story">Suddenly, everything goes dark and strangely silent. The only plausible explanation is that this part of the story
        hasn\'t been written yet! Luckily, there is an invisible portal to take you back to the beginning of the story so that you can keep playing.
    </string>
    <string name="Temp_Ans1">Start over!</string> // leads to T1_Story
    <string name="Temp_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    // Strings for main storyline
    <string name="T1_Story">You\'ve taken a break from studying to do some geocaching downtown. Nothing calms the nerves like hiding the small
        collectibles you find at garage sales, knowing that it may be years before someone else stumbles upon your secret. Speaking of secrets,
        that\'s an unusual looking manhole cover. It must be at least 50 years old, and judging by the dust covering it, it hasn\'t been opened in
        years. You always have a small flashlight on you, and you\'re tempted to go in now. Or should you find a friend to come with you?</string>
    <string name="T1_Ans1">Go in now!</string> // leads to T2_Story
    <string name="T1_Ans2">Safety in numbers. Find a friend.</string> // leads to T3_Story

    <string name="T2_Story">With some serious tugging, the manhole cover lifts off and exposes a 10 foot deep hole. The stone wall has some rusty
        metal rungs suitable for climbing. As you carefully lower yourself to the uneven stone floor below, you turn on your flashlight with a slight
        click. These tunnels have seen better days for sure! Do you examine the immediate area, or move on?</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans1">Examine the area.</string> // leads to T4_Story
    <string name="T2_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to T5_Story

    <string name="T3_Story">Despite your curiosity, you realize that no one knows where you are. It would be wise to bring someone with you in case
        something happens underground. Two of your friends come to mind, either Elaine or Greg. Elaine is likely studying at the library right now,
        and she has a lot of knowledge about the city\'s history. Greg is usually at the gym at this hour. He\'s always up for an adventure, and his
        strength could come in handy.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans1">Take Elaine.</string> // leads to E6_Story
    <string name="T3_Ans2">Take Greg.</string> // leads to G7_Story

    <string name="T4_Story">After spending a few moments poking under some loose rocks, you do not find anything useful. A few tiny bugs scurry off,
        perturbed by your rough handling of their hiding spots. While investigating the area, you do hear a faint indiscernible noise down the left
        tunnel. However, the right tunnel seems ominously quiet. Which way do you go?</string>
    <string name="T4_Ans1">Go left.</string> // leads to T8_Story
    <string name="T4_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to T9_Story

    <string name="T5_Story">Lets not waste time turning over rocks. You can go left or right. Which do you choose?</string>
    <string name="T5_Ans1">Go left</string> // leads to T8_Story
    <string name="T5_Ans2">Go right</string> // leads to T9_Story

    <string name="T8_Story">The left passage opens into a small room in which the walls and ceiling have somewhat crumbled away with time. All around
        the floor you see trash and debris of times gone by - various rusty bits of cans, silverware, etc., along with faded and torn papers... old
        newspapers maybe? Further down the tunnels sounds the running water. Do you take the time to go through the debris, or move on down the
        tunnels? Your flashlight beam shows the tunnel continues forward, or you can go through the crack in the wall to your right.</string>
    <string name="T8_Ans1">Search the debris.</string> // leads to T14_Story
    <string name="T8_Ans2">Move on!</string> // leads to T15_Story

    <string name="T9_Story">You follow the right passage, which soon opens into a large underground area. Mining cart tracks can be seen running as far
        as you can see to the left, but to the right it seems there was a cave in of some sort which has buried the tracks and blocked the path. One of
        the carts sits still on its tracks. Nearby you see what looks to be a lift.</string>
    <string name="T9_Ans1">Inspect the area.</string> // leads to T20_Story
    <string name="T9_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to T21_Story

    <string name="T14_Story">One of the stones moves slightly underfoot. Underneath you find an aged letter which seems to be somewhat intact! It
        reads: \'Dear Stranger, Herein you will find the last will and testament of James --- As I have no living heirs, I leave my trea--- to you.
        That is to say that it is yours if you can --- Where the eye is before the E, the stars surround her. In God she trusts, but --- believes in
        one ideal above others. Find it, and a small fortune --- yours.\' Let\'s go find it! Straight ahead, the tunnel continues on, but there is a
        crack in the wall to the right.</string>
    <string name="T14_Ans1">Go forward.</string> // leads to T26_Story
    <string name="T14_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to T27_Story

    <string name="T15_Story">Lets not waste time digging through newspapers. You can continue forward down the tunnel, or explore a crack in the wall
        to your right.</string>
    <string name="T15_Ans1">Go forward.</string> // leads to T26_Story
    <string name="T15_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to T27_Story

    <string name="T20_Story">Upon further inspection, it looks like the lift has seen better days. The chains and levers that work it seem to have
        rusted and become unusable. You check the mine cart, but it\'s empty and rusted. As you look at the rocks, you see something flash white very
        briefly. You hop up on the rocks and look at it at an angle, and see that some poor unfortunate person from days past got trapped under rocks!
        You briefly give your condolences before hurriedly making your way down the tracks.</string>
    <string name="T20_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T20_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to T21_Story

    <string name="T21_Story">You continue down the wide tunnel and follow the tracks. The dirt and rocks crunch loudly beneath your shoes, emphasized
        by the echo they make. Various faint foreign noises float through the tunnels, like whispers of times gone by. Some orbs float past your
        light and give the place an eerie feel, so you quicken your pace just a bit and hurry on.</string>
    <string name="T21_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T21_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to T32_Story

    <string name="T26_Story">As you continue exploring, the sound of rushing water is unmistakable; you imagine not too much further down you should
        be able to see it soon! Meanwhile the tunnels have become a lot rougher... as if this area was haphazardly chipped away by some diggers. All
        around are various chunks of rock, and some scattered tracks of small critters. Do you wish to go straight, towards the sound of water? Or
        explore where the diggers went, and go left?</string>
    <string name="T26_Ans1">Go straight.</string> // leads to T33_Story
    <string name="T26_Ans2">Go left.</string> // leads to T38_Story

    <string name="T27_Story">You squeeze your way into the crack, which opens up into a small cave. As you start exploring the cave, from the opening
        you hear someone say \"Hello? Is someone down here?\" Though you may try to hide, there really isn\'t anywhere else to go. Inevitably you see
        a light shine your way, and with a sigh they say \"Excuse me, you are trespassing here and need to leave. Please come with me.\" Uh oh...
        busted!</string>
    <string name="T27_Ans1">Try again!</string> // leads to T1_Story
    <string name="T27_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    <string name="T32_Story">After what seemed like an eternity of following the tracks, but was probably only 15 minutes or so, you notice an odd
        tunnel veering off diagonally to the left of you. It looks like whoever was digging down here found something interesting and carved out a
        spidery path. Flecks of something metallic can be seen coating the floor. Do you wish to examine the area better? Maybe go down this tunnel
        and away from the tracks? Or keep following the tracks and see where they go? Hmm.</string>
    <string name="T32_Ans1">Investigate the flecks.</string> // leads to T39_Story
    <string name="T32_Ans2">Move on!</string> // leads to T44_Story

    <string name="T33_Story">The tunnel breaks into an underwater river that rushes merrily past you. You flash your light across the water and
        notice a natural cave entrance on the other side angling up and going further in. You would have to cross the river, but it looks to be
        shallow in enough spots to safely cross. To your left a dug out tunnel continues which might be worth exploring. Which way do you go?</string>
    <string name="T33_Ans1">Cross the river.</string> // leads to T45_Story
    <string name="T33_Ans2">Explore the tunnels.</string> // leads to T110_Story

    <string name="T38_Story">In this part of the tunnel rests a heaping load of various broken things. You see what appears to be broken mine picks,
        discarded cans, splintered shovels, bits of old paper, and pieces of torn clothing. Mixed in with this are heaping loads of rocks, as if it
        all got jumbled together before being dumped off here. When you accidentally kick a can, a rat scurries off squeaking noisily. You are fairly
        certain there are more down here by the looks of it. You can continue off to your right, or keep going straight ahead through these tunnels.
        Do you wish to search or continue on?"</string>
    <string name="T38_Ans1">Search for treasure!</string> // leads to T51_Story
    <string name="T38_Ans2">Move on!</string> // leads to T56_Story

    <string name="T39_Story">You lightly touch the dust and rub it between your fingers a bit. Is this silver? Not sure, but interesting nevertheless.
        While checking that out, something else catches your eye as another metallic glint. You make your way over to where you saw the glint, and
        with a bit of poking around, you manage to find a small silvery-looking rock! You decide to bring it with you for good luck. Now where to go
        next? I wonder if the tunnel will have more neat things like the silvery rock, or if the tracks will lead to someplace interesting.</string>
    <string name="T39_Ans1">Explore the tunnel.</string> // leads to T57_Story
    <string name="T39_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to T62_Story

    <string name="T44_Story">Lets not waste time digging through metallic flecks.</string>
    <string name="T44_Ans1">Explore the tunnel.</string> // leads to T57_Story
    <string name="T44_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to T62_Story

    <string name="T45_Story">You wade into the river a bit -- ooh that\'s cold! -- and make your way across using the shallow spots to guide you.
        The water is moving rather powerfully, more so than you expected, but by keeping out of the deep spots you manage to make your way across
        and into the cave. Hopefully nothing got too wet! The cave itself it\'s definitely interesting, especially since you've never seen what
        stalactites and stalagmites looked like in person before. Angling to your right there is another cave opening that you think you could reach
        if you climbed just a bit. Let's see where this goes...</string>
    <string name="T45_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T45_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to T63_Story

    <string name="T50_Story">Heading back</string>
    <string name="T50_Ans1"></string> // leads to T
    <string name="T50_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T51_Story">When you start to search around, more rats start popping out of the piles and scurry off in various directions. You are
        pretty sure this is the proverbial \'rat\'s nest\' that folks usually only joke about. Unfortunately, nothing turns up of use or value. Oh
        well! Onwards we go! Now the question is, forward or to the right?</string>
    <string name="T51_Ans1">Go straight.</string> // leads to T105_Story
    <string name="T51_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to T110_Story

    <string name="T56_Story">Let\'s not dig through more trash. You can go straight or turn right.</string>
    <string name="T56_Ans1">Go straight.</string> // leads to T105_Story
    <string name="T56_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to T110_Story

    <string name="T57_Story">Down the tunnel you go, and where it stops, nobody knows! Speaking of which, you remind yourself that nobody knows you are
        down here, and so the excitement of adventure gives way to a bit of paranoia. Something clatters nearby which startles you a bit! You flash your
        light over, but it looks like it was only a loose rock that shifted and fell... because they do that... right? You quicken your pace a bit and
        hurry on down the tunnel, hoping to not get a different answer to that question!</string>
    <string name="T57_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T57_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to T74_Story

    <string name="T62_Story">You make your way in what appears to be a junction of some sort. The tracks continue down the tunnel, but now there is
        another set that lead away down the left. In the middle is a circular contraption that looks like was used to change the direction of a mine
        cart. All around here are various discarded tools used for mining. You notice an old pickaxe, a rusty lantern, and a shovel; all of which are
        haphazardly lying about in various states of disrepair. An old mine cart is toppled over off to the side, and some sort of noise is coming from
        it. Do you wish to investigate? Or is it time to go down one of the tunnels?</string>
    <string name="T62_Ans1">Investigate the noise.</string> // leads to T75_Story
    <string name="T62_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to T81_Story

    <string name="T63_Story">As you work your way up, the climb takes about as much effort as a steep hike, and you make your way to the top... a
        bit muddy if nothing else. As you continue on, there is a natural arch that overlooks the river where you can hear the water quickly
        rushing - how cool! But wait, what\'s that further on down? Another cave? Another dig site? It looks like someone setup a camp here, but
        decades ago. What catches your eye is another glint of something metallic, near a sack of some sort. Coins? The river looks particularly
        dangerous here, in a tighter spot than where you crossed last. Do you want to brave it and go check out the camp site? Or turn back because
        it could be really dangerous this time?</string>
    <string name="T63_Ans1">Brave the river!</string> // leads to T92_Story
    <string name="T63_Ans2">Turn back.</string> // leads to T86_Story

    <string name="T68_Story">Continue tunnels by river</string>
    <string name="T68_Ans1"></string> // leads to T
    <string name="T68_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T69_Story">Continue tunnels by river</string>
    <string name="T69_Ans1"></string> // leads to T
    <string name="T69_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T74_Story">While making your way further down the tunnel, you start to hear a faint *whooshing* noise coming from further ahead. A
        squishy, gurgly, grumbly noise emanates from your stomach, and you realise that it\'s been a bit before you had something to eat. Fortunately
        you remembered to at least grab an energy bar before heading out, and quickly unwrap and devour it. A quick swig from your water bottle washes
        it down, before you realize that you don\'t have much more left. Feeling reinvigorated, you press on!</string>
    <string name="T74_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T74_Ans2"></string> // leads to T98_Story

    <string name="T75_Story">As as quietly as you can, you make your way over to the mine cart. Before you are almost there, a large brown rat hops out
        from around the corner, eyes gleaming white with the reflection from your flashlight. It stands on its hind legs, and gives you a few cursory
        sniffs with a twitch of its whiskers before scampering back into the cart. Let's leave that little fella alone and go find something more
        interesting to look at. You hear a faint noise down the left tunnel, but the one ahead of you is silent. Which way now?</string>
    <string name="T75_Ans1">Explore new tunnel.</string> // leads to T57_Story
    <string name="T75_Ans2">Continue straight.</string> // leads to T111_Story

    <string name="T80_Story"></string>
    <string name="T80_Ans1"></string> // leads to T
    <string name="T80_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T81_Story">Moving on without investigating noise.</string>
    <string name="T81_Ans1">Left new tunnel.</string> // leads to T57_Story
    <string name="T81_Ans2">Straight.</string> // leads to T111_Story

    <string name="T86_Story">Continue animal tracks</string>
    <string name="T86_Ans1"></string> // leads to T
    <string name="T86_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T87_Story">Continue animal tracks</string>
    <string name="T87_Ans1"></string> // leads to T
    <string name="T87_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T92_Story">You look around for a way down, and manage to find a rocky area that seems to have enough hand and foot holds to get
        down to the river. As you start to climb down, the rocks come out from your grasp! OH NO! *SPLASH!* You fall into the river and briefly try
        to orient yourself before hitting your head on something that hurts! ...as all goes black... another soul claimed by the temptations of these
        ancient tunnels.</string>
    <string name="T92_Ans1">Try again!</string> // leads to T1_Story
    <string name="T92_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    <string name="T93_Story">Turning back from second crossing</string>
    <string name="T93_Ans1"></string> // leads to T
    <string name="T93_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T98_Story">There is definitely some sort of water making noise further ahead. You can feel the tunnels getting damper, and see little
        mushrooms along the floors. Various tiny critters skitter away at your light, finding solace in cracks and crannies in the rock. A faint odor
        is in the air, like the smell of a hamster cage... how odd! You press on, curious about this new change.</string>
    <string name="T98_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T98_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to T99_Story

    <string name="T99_Story">Making your way down the tunnel, you come to the edge of river. It\'s moving pretty fast here, going over various rocks and
        other debris. Nearby, you notice what was making the weird smell. It looks like a colony of bats have made their home here, and the smell is
        coming from their guano. Various roaches seem to have made their home in the guano, so you give all that a wide berth. Across the river looks
        like someone set up a camp here, but decades ago. What catches your eye is a glint of something metallic, near a sack of some sort. Coins? An
        old wood bridge, broken in the middle now, seems to have been how folks made their way across in the past. Do you search around for a way across,
        or is it time to head back down a different route?</string>
    <string name="T99_Ans1">Search around.</string> // leads to T104_Story
    <string name="T99_Ans2">Head back.</string> // leads to T50_Story

    <string name="T104_Story">Looking around, you see a log that looks like it could span the gap, but it\'s too heavy for you to move - drat! While
        poking around, you notice that the bats are starting to move around a bit more, and have a vision of all of those movies you watched as a kid
        where people get swarmed by them. Let's not see if that actually happens - time to go explore elsewhere. You make your way back down the tunnel
        with a sigh.</string>
    <string name="T104_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T104_Ans2"></string> // leads to T

    <string name="T105_Story">Now this is interesting! Crystal-looking stalagmites and stalagtites jut from the floor and ceiling of this cavern, glowing
        a pale white in your light. Are these quartz crystals maybe? You break off a smaller one and squirrel it away to look at later. Nothing else here
        seems to pique your interest. You look around and notice that the cave continues to your right - Let\'s see where it leads!</string>
    <string name="T105_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="T105_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to T

    <string name="T110_Story">The tunnel opens up to a large underground river that gurgles merrily. The light from your flashlight catches various
        sparkly bits which illuminates the water with a slight disco ball pattern. Other things seem to be reflecting from down one tunnel. The other way
        the river continues which can be followed.</string>
    <string name="T110_Ans1">Investigate reflection.</string> // leads to T
    <string name="T110_Ans2">Follow the river.</string> // leads to T

    <string name="T111_Story">As you follow the tracks, off to your right you see a chute of some sort leading up and into another room.  Through this
        chute you can feel air blowing past you and on down where you came from. Nearby, an old and rickety-looking ladder heads up and over in the
        direction of the chute. All around you there are rocks of various sizes cluttering the ground. Further on the tracks and tunnel continue. Do you
        wish to go up the ladder, or continue down the tracks?</string>
    <string name="T111_Ans1">Climb the ladder!</string> // leads to T
    <string name="T111_Ans2">Continue down the tunnel.</string> // leads to T

    <string name="T116_Story"></string>
    <string name="T116_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="T116_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="T117_Story"></string>
    <string name="T117_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="T117_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="T122_Story"></string>
    <string name="T122_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="T122_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="T123_Story"></string>
    <string name="T123_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="T123_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="T128_Story"></string>
    <string name="T128_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="T128_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="T129_Story"></string>
    <string name="T129_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="T129_Ans2"></string>



    // Strings for Elaine's storyline
    <string name="E6_Story">Elaine is nervous about going underground, but she can\'t resist the opportunity to discover more of your city\'s history.
        She packs a backpack that would make a certain umbrella carrying nanny proud, and you return to start your adventure. With some serious
        tugging, the manhole cover lifts off and exposes a 10 foot deep hole. The stone wall has metal rungs suitable for climbing. You carefully
        lower yourself to the uneven stone floor below and Elaine timidly follows. Your flashlight beam shows a wide passage to the left and another
        to the right.</string>
    <string name="E6_Ans1">Check out the area.</string> // leads to E10_Story
    <string name="E6_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to E11_Story

    <string name="E10_Story">After spending a few moments poking under some loose rocks, you do not find anything useful. A few tiny bugs scurry off,
        perturbed by your rough handling of their hiding spots. While investigating the area, you do hear a faint indiscernible noise down the left
        tunnel. However, the right tunnel seems ominously quiet. Which way do you go?</string>
    <string name="E10_Ans1">Go left.</string> // leads to E16_Story
    <string name="E10_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to E17_Story

    <string name="E11_Story">Lets not waste time turning over rocks. You can go left or right. Which do you choose?</string>
    <string name="E11_Ans1">Go left.</string> // leads to E16_Story
    <string name="E11_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to E17_Story

    <string name="E16_Story">The left passage opens into a small room. One of the stones moves slightly underfoot. Underneath Elaine finds an aged
        letter, mostly intact. It reads: \'Dear Stranger, Herein you will find the last will and testament of James ---  As I have no living heirs, I
        leave my trea--- to you. That is to say that it is yours if you can --- Where the eye is before the E, the stars surround her. In God she
        trusts, but --- believes in one ideal above others. Find it, and a small fortune --- yours.\' Straight ahead, the passage continues on, but
        there is an additional larger passage to the right.</string>
    <string name="E16_Ans1">Go forward.</string> // leads to E22_Story
    <string name="E16_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to E23_Story

    <string name="E17_Story">You follow the right passage, which soon opens into a large underground area. Mining cart tracks can be seen running as
        far as you can see to the left, but to the right it seems there was a cave in of some sort which has buried the tracks and blocked the path.
        One of the carts sits still on its tracks. Nearby you see what looks to be a lift. Elaine thinks this used to be where ore would be brought
        to be smelted in the building above, and that this used to be an active silver mine ages ago. Shall we look around for some goodies? Or follow
        the tracks?</string>
    <string name="E17_Ans1">Inspect the area.</string> // leads to E28_Story
    <string name="E17_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to E29_Story

    <string name="E22_Story">As you continue exploring, the sound of rushing water is unmistakable; you imagine not too much further down you should
        be able to see it soon! Meanwhile the tunnels have become a lot rougher... as if this area was haphazardly chipped away by some diggers. All
        around are various chunks of rock, and some scattered tracks of small critters. Elaine shies away from the tracks, but you assure her you've
        seen no recent evidence of vermin. Elaine thinks this area might have been a mine at some point. Do you wish to go straight, towards the sound
        of water? Or explore where the diggers went, and go left?</string>
    <string name="E22_Ans1">Go straight.</string> // leads to E34_Story
    <string name="E22_Ans2">Go left.</string> // leads to E35_Story

    <string name="E23_Story">You squeeze your way into the crack, but Elaine gets a look on her face which indicates that\'s not going to happen with
        her! This opens up into a small cave, and as you start exploring the cave, from the opening you hear a scream from Elaine, and then a
        startled \"Hello? Is someone down here?\" Inevitibly you see a light shine your way, and with a sigh they say \"Excuse me, you are
        trespassing here and need to leave. Please come with me.\" Uh oh... busted! Do you want to play again?</string>
    <string name="E23_Ans1">Try again.</string> // Leads to T1_Story
    <string name="E23_Ans2">Play later.</string> // Ends game and leads to End_Story

    <string name="E28_Story">Upon further inspection, it looks like the lift has seen better days. The chains and levers that work it seem to have
        rusted and become unusable. You check the mine cart, but it\'s empty and rusted. As you look at the rocks, you see something flash white very
        briefly. You hop up on the rocks and look at it at an angle, and see that some poor unfortunate person from days past got trapped under rocks!
        You don\'t want to spook Elaine this quickly into the exploration, so you mumble something about \"...big, heavy, rocks...\" and hurriedly
        make your way down the tracks.</string>
    <string name="E28_Ans1"></string> // This button will be hidden
    <string name="E28_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to E29_Story

    <string name="E29_Story">You continue down the wide tunnel and follow the tracks. The dirt and rocks crunch loudly beneath your shoes, emphasized
        by the echo they make. Various faint foreign noises float through the tunnels, like whispers of times gone by. Some orbs float past you light
        and give the place an eerie feel. Elaine grasps onto your arm while you walk. She mentions that she read that orbs can sometimes be spirits
        floating by, but that\'s just nonsense, right? You both look at each other for a moment, and then quicken your pace a bit.</string>
    <string name="E29_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E29_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to E40_Story

    <string name="E34_Story">The tunnel breaks into an underwater river that rushes merrily past you. You flash your light across the water and
        notice a natural cave entrance on the other side angling up and going further in. You would have to cross the river, but it looks to be
        shallow in enough spots to safely cross. Elaine looks at the cave, and then back to you before saying \"There is no way I am crossing that!
        You are on your own if you want to cross and poke around in there!\" To your left a dug out tunnel continues which might be worth exploring.
        Which way do you go?</string>
    <string name="E34_Ans1">Cross alone.</string> // leads to E41_Story
    <string name="E34_Ans2">Go left with Elaine.</string> // leads to E58_Story

    <string name="E35_Story">In this part of the tunnel rests a heaping load of various broken things. You see what appears to be broken mine picks,
        discarded cans, splintered shovels, bits of old paper, and pieces of torn clothing. Mixed in with this are heaping loads of rocks, as if it all
        got jumbled together before being dumped off here. When you accidentally kick a can, a rat scurries off squeaking noisily which makes Elaine
        scream and go down the next tunnel with a "NOPE! NOPE! NOPE!" trailing after her. Let's go catch up with her!</string>
    <string name="E35_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E35_Ans2">Follow Elaine!</string> // leads to E46_Story

    <string name="E40_Story">After what seemed like an eternity of following the tracks, but was probably only 15 minutes or so, you both notice an
        odd tunnel veering off diagonally to the left of you. It looks like whoever was digging down here found something interesting and carved out
        a spidery path. Elaine mentions this was definitely a mine vein! Flecks of something metallic can be seen coating the floor which Elaine
        suspects to be either Iron or Silver. Do you wish to examine the area better? Maybe go down this tunnel and away from the tracks? Or keep
        following the tracks and see where they go?</string>
    <string name="E40_Ans1">Investigate the flecks.</string> // leads to E52_Story
    <string name="E40_Ans2">Move on!</string> // leads to E53_Story

    <string name="E41_Story">You wade into the river a bit -- ooh that\'s cold! -- and make your way across using the shallow spots to guide you.
        The water is moving rather powerfully, more so than you expected, but by keeping out of the deep spots you manage to make your way across and
        into the cave. Hopefully nothing got too wet! The cave itself it\'s definitely interesting, especially since you\'ve never seen what stalactites
        and stalagmites looked like in person before. Angling to your right there is another cave opening that you think you could reach if you
        climbed just a bit. Let\'s see where this goes...</string>
    <string name="E41_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E41_Ans2">Continue</string> // leads to E59_Story

    <string name="E46_Story">You catch up with Elaine who looks to have completely forgotten what she was running from. Now this is interesting!
        Crystal-looking stalagmites and stalagtites jut from the floor and ceiling of this cavern, glowing a pale white in your light. Are these quartz
        crystals maybe? You break off a smaller one and squirrel it away to look at later. Nothing else here seems to pique your interest. You look
        around and notice that the cave continues on - Let\'s see where it leads!</string>
    <string name="E46_Ans1"></string> // lthis button will be hidden
    <string name="E46_Ans2"></string> // leads to E47_Story

    <string name="E47_Story">As you both make your way further into the crystal caves, you have to squint a bit, as the light reflecting off of them
        somewhat blinding! It\'s like you stepped into a large geode made of huge white crystals! You both \"Oooh!\" and \"Wow!\" at the sight before
        you. This area is very serene, and almost hums as you look around. Or maybe that noise is water? You definitely hear water further up. After
        taking a quick picture, and giving Elaine a minute to break off a small crystal, you both gingerly make your way between the massive
        crystals.</string>
    <string name="E47_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E47_Ans2">Follow the sound.</string> // leads to E58_Story

    <string name="E52_Story">Elaine lightly touch the dust and rubs it between her fingers a bit. This is definitely silver! While she is checking
        that out, something else catches your eye as another metallic glint. You make your way over to where you saw the glint, and with a bit of
        poking around, you manage to find a small chunk of silver! You decide to bring it with you for good luck. Now where to go next? I wonder if
        the tunnel will have more neat things, or if the tracks will lead to someplace interesting.</string>
    <string name="E52_Ans1">Explore the tunnel.</string> // leads to E70_Story
    <string name="E52_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to E71_Story

    <string name="E53_Story">Lets not waste time digging through metallic flecks.</string>
    <string name="E53_Ans1">Explore the tunnel.</string> // leads to E70_Story
    <string name="E53_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to E71_Story

    <string name="E58_Story">The tunnel opens up to a large underground river that gurgles merrily. The light from your flashlight catches various
        sparkly bits which illuminates the water with a slight disco ball pattern. Elaine is fascinated by the small crystals which seem to be
        reflecting the light. The river continues which can be followed.</string>
    <string name="E58_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden.
    <string name="E58_Ans2">Follow the river.</string> // leads to E

    <string name="E59_Story">As you work your way up, the climb takes about as much effort as a steep hike, and you make your way to the top... a bit
        muddy if nothing else. As you continue on, there is a natural arch that overlooks the river where you can hear the water quickly rushing -
        how cool! But wait, what\'s that further on down? Another cave? Another dig site? It looks like someone setup a camp here, but decades ago.
        What catches your eye is another glint of something metallic, near a sack of some sort. Coins? The river looks particularly dangerous here,
        in a tighter spot than where you crossed last. Do you want to brave it and go check out the camp site? Or turn back because it could be really
        dangerous this time?</string>
    <string name="E59_Ans1">Brave the river.</string>// leads to E64_Story
    <string name="E59_Ans2">Return to Elaine.</string> // leads to E65_Story

    <string name="E64_Story">You look around for a way down, and manage to find a rocky area that seems to have enough hand and foot holds to get
        down to the river. As you start to climb down, the rocks come out from your grasp! OH NO! *SPLASH!* You fall into the river and briefly try
        to orient yourself before hitting your head on something that hurts! ...as all goes black... another soul claimed by the temptations of these
        ancient tunnels.</string>
    <string name="E64_Ans1">Try again?</string> // leads to T1_Story
    <string name="E64_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    <string name="E65_Story">Returning to Elaine.</string>
    <string name="E65_Ans1"></string> // leads to E
    <string name="E65_Ans2"></string> // leads to E

    <string name="E70_Story">Down the tunnel you go, and with a happy Elaine coming with. Something clatters nearby which startles you both a bit!
        You flash your light over, but it looks like it was only a loose rock that shifted and fell. Elaine has you shine your light all around until
        she is certain that some crazy monster isn't coming after you. You both quicken your pace a bit and hurry on down the tunnel, hoping to not to
        have missed anything!</string>
    <string name="E70_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E70_Ans2">Moving on.</string> // leads to E76_Story

    <string name="E71_Story">You make your way in what appears to be a junction of some sort. The tracks continue down the tunnel, but now there is
        another set that lead away down the left. In the middle is a circular contraption that Elaine says was used to change the direction of a mine
        cart. All around here are various discarded tools used for mining. You notice an old pickaxe, a rusty lantern, and a shovel; all of which are
        haphazardly lying about in various states of disrepair. An old minecart is toppled over off to the side, and some sort of noise is coming from
        it. Elaine squeaks and gives you a frantic look - time to go!</string>
    <string name="E71_Ans1">New tracks.</string> // leads to E70_Story
    <string name="E71_Ans2">Same tracks.</string> // leads to E88_Story

    <string name="E76_Story">While making your way further down the tunnel, you start to hear a faint *whooshing* noise coming from further ahead. A
        squishy, gurgly, grumbly noise emanates from your stomach, and you realise that it\'s been a bit before you had something to eat. Fortunately
        Elaine remembered to grab some food and drinks before heading out, and you both take a quick break to satiate yourselves before moving on.
        Feeling reinvigorated, you press on!</string>
    <string name="E76_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E76_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to E77_Story

    <string name="E77_Story">There is definitely some sort of water making noise further ahead. You can feel the tunnels getting damper, and see little
        mushrooms along the floors. Various tiny critters skitter away at your light, finding solace in cracks and crannies in the rock. A faint odor
        is in the air, like the smell of a hamster cage... how odd! You mention this to Elaine, who was warily eyeing the bugs. She sniffs the air, and
        then grimaces a bit before mentioning to you that there are probably bats where we are headed. You cautiously make your way along the tracks,
        keeping an eye above you and on the ground for signs.</string>
    <string name="E77_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E77_Ans2">Head back.</string> // leads to E82_Story

    <string name="E82_Story">Making your way down the tunnel, you come to the edge of river. It\'s moving pretty fast here, going over various rocks and
        other debris. Nearby, you find a colony of bats have made their home here, and the smell is coming from their guano. Various roaches seem to
        have made their home in the guano, so both of you give all that a wide berth. Across the river looks like someone set up a camp here, but decades
        ago. What catches your eye is a glint of something metallic, near a sack of some sort. Coins? An old wood bridge, broken in the middle now, seems
        to have been how folks made their way across in the past. Do you search around for a way across, or is it time to head back down a different
        route?</string>
    <string name="E82_Ans1">Search around.</string> // leads to E83_Story
    <string name="E82_Ans2">Go back.</string> // leads to E

    <string name="E83_Story">While you search around, Elaine finds herself a spot as far away from the bats and bugs as possible. To your surprise, she
        says she\'s found something over there, and calls you over to see it. It seems that there is a crack in the cave wall which leads further on
        along the river. Maybe there is a safe way across?</string>
    <string name="E83_Ans1">Explore batcave.</string> // leads to E89_Story
    <string name="E83_Ans2">Return to tracks.</string> // leads to E

    <string name="E88_Story">As you follow the tracks, off to your right you see a chute of some sort leading up and into another room.  Through this
        chute you can feel air blowing past you and on down where you came from. Nearby, an old and rickety-looking ladder heads up and over in the
        direction of the chute. All around you there are rocks of various sizes cluttering the ground. Elaine explains that this chute was used to drop
        ore into the mine carts, and that there is probably an air vent further up. Further on the tracks and tunnel continue. Do you wish to go up the
        ladder, or continue down the tracks?</string>
    <string name="E88_Ans1">Climb the ladder!</string> // leads to E118_Story
    <string name="E88_Ans2">Continue down the tunnel.</string> // leads to E

    <string name="E89_Story">As you join Elaine in exploring this tunnel, she comments that at one time ages ago this might have been a lava tube of some
        sort. Ages have passed since then, as sediment has made its way to here, possibly during times of flooding. Further down the tunnel you see light!
        Let\'s see where this goes!</string>
    <string name="E89_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E89_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to E94_Story

    <string name="E94_Story">The tunnel snakes around and opens up into a much larger area. Sand crunches underfoot, and you continue to hear the rush of
        the river nearby. At this point a flashlight is no longer needed as there is enough light to see without it. A few insects scamper out of the way
        as you and Elaine make your way towards the ever-brightening light. Elaine stops for a moment to marvel at the design made from ages past. A quick
        picture here and there, and off you go! A breeze wafts in, carrying with it the scent of nearby foliage.</string>
    <string name="E94_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E94_Ans2">Follow the light!</string> // leads to E95_Story

    <string name="E95_Story">As you and Elaine round a bend in the tunnel, it opens up to a waterfall making its way down into a nearby forest. At this
        angle you see various hills and trees poking out around you. This spot is very serene, so you both take a quick break to appreciate it. During this
        time you notice that it\'s late afternoon, and that you\'ve both been walking for hours without realizing it. How far have you come you wonder? As
        you get up to stretch, you notice that the cave continues on the opposite side of the waterfall. A large jumble of logs at the edge of the
        waterfall might have presented you with a natural bridge. You tentatively give them a kick here and there, then ease yourself on top before making
        your way across. None of them budge even an inch, seemingly stuck fast to the rocks. After quite a bit of coaxing, and hand-holding, Elaine
        reluctantly follows.</string>
    <string name="E95_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E95_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to E100_Story

    <string name="E100_Story">Continuing down the other side of the river, it seems more lava tubes have carved out some natural tunnels. As you progress
        deeper, the light dimishes, and you resume using your flashlights again. You aren\'t sure how much longer these ones will last, but Elaine assures
        you that she brought backup ones just in case. It definitely helps to have smart friends! Further on the tunnel breaks open to give you another
        view of the river. Are you heading in the direction of the camp site you saw earlier? It sure seems like it!</string>
    <string name="E100_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E100_Ans2">Follow the tubes.</string> // leads to E101_Story

    <string name="E101_Story">To your dismay, the tunnel ends near where you saw the camp, but not quite to it. Shoot! You and Elaine take a moment to
        watch the river, and a small flurry of bats making their way down the river towards the cave entrance. It must be getting dark if they have decided
        to make their way on out. You and Elaine site down to discuss your options since you still need to make your way back home. You want to search
        around just in case anything was missed, but Elaine is tired, sore, and wants to head home. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="E101_Ans1">5 more minutes!</string> // leads to E106_Story
    <string name="E101_Ans2">Go home.</string>

    <string name="E106_Story">After some epic begging and giving Elaine a few promises of favors yet to come, she gives you a bit of time to check out the
        area before heading on home. You make the best of it and double-check all the areas you previously looked at without finding anything. Feeling a
        bit defeated, you flop down on the rocky sand for a minute to ponder things out. Not long into this process, you are interrupted with a tiny screech
        coming from above you. You quickly flash your light over to where it came from, and see a bat crawling out of a horizontal hole about 15 feet up that
        you previously overlooked as it was obscured by a stalactite. It quickly flies off, but then another comes out and joins it. How odd. Piquing your
        curiosity, you cauthiously climb up and peer in. No more bats, but it does look like it leads to another area! On top of it, you are fairly certain
        it\'s wide enough to crawl through. The drawback here would be crawling through bat guano... ick! Elaine wants no part of all that! Do you wish to
        go in alone? Or is it time to head back?</string>
    <string name="E106_Ans1">Continue alone!</string> // leads to E107_Story
    <string name="E106_Ans2">Go home.</string>

    <string name="E107_Story">You crawl through the small opening, and sure enough it dumps out on the other side to where the mining camp is at! Rather
        ungracefully you make your way out of the crawl space and into the camp. Here you see a couple of small tents, areas where people slept, and various
        litter of old cans, utensils, etc. lying about in the sand. Nearby a table rests against one of the walls with various writing instruments. Most
        importantly, the prize you were seeking is here. A small bag with a few coins spilling out is nearby. You brush them off and empty out the contents.
        Various silvery things are within, small chunks of silver, coins, a tooth? Wow, quite the eclectic collection here! As you marvel at it, you hear
        Elaine asking if everything is alright, to which you excitedly reply it is! With a hoot, you take your prize and make your way back to her. You show
        her your find and decide to make your way back home. Throughout the trek you excitedly discuss the various knickknacks this sack holds, vowing to
        come back sometime soon to explore more!</string>
    <string name="E107_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E107_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to E112_Story

    <string name="E112_Story">We hope you have enjoyed the story so far! Please keep an eye out for the next adventure as this one was just a teaser for more
        to come!</string>
    <string name="E112_Ans1">Play again!</string> // leads to T1_Story
    <string name="E112_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    <string name="E113_Story">Elaine is right, it\'s getting dark and there is a LOT of walking ahead of you in order to get back home. With a sigh you both
        get back to your feet and start the long walk back. During this time you both talk about how cool this adventure was, and to set a date to come back
        and explore some more!</string>
    <string name="E113_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E113_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    <string name="E118_Story">You eye the old wooden ladder warily, but after a few tentative bounces on the lower struts, you believe it\'s safe to climb.
        Up the ladder you go! When you reach the top you see a hole through the ceiling that is mostly blocked off, but air is still passing through. This spot
        looks like a crude chute, for ore maybe? As you ponder this, you hear some some eerie noises... whispers maybe? ...faint and indistinct near you.
        Hopefully that\'s just the wind, but just in case, let's get out of here and move on! You come back down and look a bit pale to Elaine, before hastily
        making your way further down the tracks.</string>
    <string name="E118_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E118_Ans2">Move faster.</string> // leads to E119_Story

    <string name="E119_Story">As you both make your way down the tunnel, you continue to feel a faint breeze move past you. All around the floor, streaky
        patterns show the wind had some fun creating art. How neat! Elaine stops you to take a few pictures. Now you are both curious where this tunnel ends;
        I mean, it has to at some place right? Elaine looks lost in thought as you make your way further down.</string>
    <string name="E119_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="E119_Ans2">Moving on.</string> // leads to E124_Story

    <string name="E124_Story">The tunnel abruptly ends at another cave-in - drat! You hear the wind blowing through the cracks in the mess before you, making
        an occasional whistle or hum. As you peer through the cracks, you notice something interesting on the other side - a desk! How odd. You confer with
        Elaine, and she has a sudden epitome about where you are at! There is an old mine that's a few miles outside of town, which has been boarded up...
        and this might be it! Do you wish to try and find a way past the cave-in? Or turn around and explore elsewhere?</string>
    <string name="E124_Ans1">Search</string> // leads to E125_Story
    <string name="E124_Ans2">Turn around.</string>

    <string name="E125_Story">You carefully examine the rocks before you to try and figure out a way past them. There are a few places where you can fit your
        arm and some of your body through, but it all feels really claustrophobic. Although... if you move here, contort a bit there, and pull yourself a bit
        over there... hmm. You are guessing you *might* fit through one area - or get horribly stuck. Elaine carefully reviews the area with you, and has a
        better idea! She saw where one of the beams was making a fulcrum, and with a bit of effort, you should be able to shift a large rock out of the way
        and crawl in. Do you want to try Elaine\'s idea? Or go explore someplace else?</string>
    <string name="E125_Ans1">Trust Elaine.</string> // leads to E130_Story
    <string name="E125_Ans2">Explore further!</string> // leads to E131_Story

    <string name="E130_Story">You decide to trust Elaine and her idea of using leverage to move one of the larger rocks out of the way. You try with your
        combined weight, but it\'s not enough to budge the rocks. Using some supplies from her pack, Elaine quickly crafts a net. You spend a bit of time
        piling up some rocks in it, then use a bit of additional leverage to hoist the rocks up a bit on the beam. The rocks creak and shift a bit, but don\'t
        move quite yet. At this point, you decided to be a little wild, and climb up the rocks to jump down on the beam! *CRACK!* The rock moves and falls out
        of the way, leaving a spot large enough to crawl through! You brush yourself off, and look around. Elaine makes her way through the opening and does
        the same. Sure enough a desk is here, with a note pinned to it by a dagger. Next to the note is a large bag, tied up at the top. You examine the note
        and it reads \"Here lies a sample of my wealth, left to whomever has the gumption and fortitude to find it. On the back of this letter is a map which
        leads to where the next clue lies.\" Below this is signed James, with a small symbol of an eye in a pyramid beneath that. You flip the note over, and
        sure enough you see a rough map to... someplace. You hand the note over to Elaine and check out the bag. After unravelling the top of it, you pour out
        a handful of 1800\'s silver dollars! There has to be at least a hundred of these by the size and weight of this bag! Quite the find! You check the time
        and realize you\'ve spent all day down here, so it\'s time for the both of you to make your way back home. You two chat excitedly about your find along
        the way back, already thinking about a plan for your next adventure!</string>
    <string name="E130_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="E130_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="E131_Story"></string>
    <string name="E131_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="E131_Ans2"></string>


    // Strings for Greg's storyline
    <string name="G7_Story">Greg doesn\'t take any convincing. With little delay, you return to the site you discovered. Greg lifts the manhole cover
        with ease and clambers down the metal rungs, skipping most of them before hopping to the uneven floor below. You hurriedly follow. Your
        flashlight beam shows a wide passage to the left and another to the right.</string>
    <string name="G7_Ans1">Inspect the area.</string> // leads to G12_Story
    <string name="G7_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to G13_Story

    <string name="G12_Story">As you start checking out the area, Greg snorts at you before giving you an exasperated look. He then points down the two
        passageways, one after the other, before looking at you expectantly. I guess he\'s right, let\'s go find something a bit more interesting than a
        dusty room and rusty metal. You do hear a faint indiscernible noise down the left tunnel. However, the right tunnel seems ominously quiet.
        Which way do you go?</string>
    <string name="G12_Ans1">Go left.</string> // leads to G18_Story
    <string name="G12_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to G19_Story

    <string name="G13_Story">Let\'s go find something a bit more interesting than a dusty room and rusty metal. You do hear a faint indiscernible noise
        down the left tunnel. However, the right tunnel seems ominously quiet. Which way do you go?</string>
    <string name="G13_Ans1">Go left.</string> // leads to G18_Story
    <string name="G13_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to G19_Story

    <string name="G18_Story">The left passage opens into a small room in which the walls and ceiling have somewhat crumbled away with time. All around
        the floor you see trash and debris of times gone by - various rusty bits of cans, silverware, etc., along with faded and torn papers... old
        newspapers maybe? Further down the tunnels sounds the running water. Do you take the time to go through the debris, or move on down the
        tunnels? Your flashlight beam shows the tunnel continues forward, or you can go through the crack in the wall to your right.</string>
    <string name="G18_Ans1">Search the debris.</string> // leads to G24_Story
    <string name="G18_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to G25_Story

    <string name="G19_Story">You two decide to follow the right passage, which soon opens into a large underground area. Mining cart tracks can be
        seen running as far as you can see to the left, but to the right it seems there was a cave in of some sort which has buried the tracks and
        blocked the path. One of the carts sits still on its tracks, and nearby you see what looks to be a lift. Greg starts \'looking for gold\'
        ...really? Do you look around with him, or continue down the tracks?</string>
    <string name="G19_Ans1">Look for gold.</string> // leads to G30_Story
    <string name="G19_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to G31_Story

    <string name="G24_Story">Before you start rummaging through the debris, Greg gets your attention - he\'s found something! Half-buried under some
        rocks, an ivory handle sticks out. Greg grabs it, and pulls out an old hunting knife! He brushes off the dirt and grime, then uses his nails
        to work away a bit of rust to show a name and date: James -- Aug 5, 1876. The rest of the name is corroded and indiscernible. At this point
        Greg is excited to continue on and see what else you can find! Straight ahead, the tunnel continues on, but there is a crack in the wall to
        the right.</string>
    <string name="G24_Ans1">Go forward.</string> // leads to G36_Story
    <string name="G24_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to G37_Story

    <string name="G25_Story">Straight ahead, the tunnel continues on, but there is a crack in the wall to the right.</string>
    <string name="G25_Ans1">Go forward.</string> // leads to G36_Story
    <string name="G25_Ans2">Go right.</string> // leads to G37_Story

    <string name="G30_Story">It looks like the lift has seen better days. The chains and levers seem to have rusted and become unusable. You check the
        mine cart, but it\'s empty and rusted; Greg seems disappointed by this. As you look at the rocks, you see something flash white very briefly.
        You hop up on the rocks and look at it at an angle, and see that some poor unfortunate person from days past got trapped under a cave-in! Greg
        quickly scampers over to look as well - it seems he has a morbid fascination for this. Time to move on my friend!</string>
    <string name="G30_Ans1"></string> // This button will be hidden
    <string name="G30_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to G42_Story

    <string name="G31_Story">As you make your way down the tracks, you think about the poor unfortunate person crushed under the rocks behind you.
        Greg sees this, and cracks a rather inappropriate joke, which you can\'t help but laugh at. You shake your head a bit and continue down the
        tracks.</string>
    <string name="G31_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="G31_Ans2">More tracks...</string> // leads to G43_Story

    <string name="G36_Story">As you continue exploring, the sound of rushing water is unmistakable; you imagine not too much further down you should
        be able to see it soon! Meanwhile the tunnels have become a lot rougher... as if this area was haphazardly chipped away by some diggers. All
        around are various chunks of rock, and some scattered tracks of small critters. Greg hears the water and excitedly runs on ahead of you!
        ...Hey! Wait up!</string>
    <string name="G36_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="G36_Ans2">Follow Greg.</string> // leads to G49_Story

    <string name="G37_Story">Greg attempts to squeeze his way into the crack, but gets stuck! OH NO! You start to panic a bit when failing to dislodge
        him! Sometime between Greg pushing, and you pulling, someone scares you when they say \"Hello? Is someone down here?\" You quickly recover and
        get their help, and with a bit of effort you get Greg pulled out of the crack in the wall... with only a little skin missing too! Ouch!
        Unfortunately for you, they also let you know that you are both trespassing and need to leave. Oh no, busted!</string>
    <string name="G37_Ans1">Try again!</string> // leads to T1_Story
    <string name="G37_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    <string name="G42_Story">As you make your way down the tracks, you think about the poor unfortunate person crushed under the rocks behind you.
        Greg sees this, and cracks a rather inappropriate joke about them being \'boned\', which you can\'t help but laugh at. You shake your head a bit
        and continue down the tracks.</string>
    <string name="G42_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="G42_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to G54_Story

    <string name="G43_Story">following the tracks without Greg</string>
    <string name="G43_Ans1"></string> // leads to G55_Story
    <string name="G43_Ans2"></string> // leads to G60_Story

    <string name="G48_Story">following the tracks without Greg</string>
    <string name="G48_Ans1"></string> // leads to G61_Story
    <string name="G48_Ans2"></string> // leads to G66_Story

    <string name="G49_Story">The tunnel breaks into an underwater river that rushes merrily past you. You flash your light across the water and both of
        you notice a natural cave entrance on the other side angling up and going further in. Before you can say anything, Greg jumps in and starts
        fording the river on his way to the cave. You let out a sigh before making your way across the river, following Greg...</string>
    <string name="G49_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="G49_Ans2">Follow Greg.</string> // leads to G67_Story

    <string name="G54_Story">After a dozen or so more terrible jokes, you two come up to a fork tunnel veering off diagonally to the left of you. It
        looks like whoever was digging down here found something interesting and carved out a spidery path. Flecks of something metallic can be seen
        coating the floor. Greg rushes over and scoops up a handful of it. It glints metallic in his hands, and he grins while pondering if it\'s worth
        anything. Do you wish to poke around in the dirt with Greg? Maybe go down this tunnel and away from the tracks? Or keep following the tracks
        and see where they go?</string>
    <string name="G54_Ans1">Dig in the dirt.</string> // leads to G72_Story
    <string name="G54_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to G73_Story

    <string name="G55_Story">Continue without Greg</string>
    <string name="G55_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G55_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G60_Story">Continue without Greg</string>
    <string name="G60_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G60_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G61_Story">Continue without Greg</string>
    <string name="G61_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G61_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G66_Story">Continuing without Greg</string>
    <string name="G66_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G66_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G67_Story">You wade into the river a bit -- ooh that\'s cold! -- and make your way across using the shallow spots to guide you. The
        water is moving rather powerfully, more so than you expected, but Greg noticed this as well and pulls you through it. You both make your way
        across and into the cave. Good, the flashlight still works! The cave itself it\'s definitely interesting, especially since you've never seen
        what stalactites and stalagmites looked like in person before. Angling to your right there is another cave opening that you think you could
        reach if you climbed just a bit. We\'ve come this far, let's see where this goes...</string>
    <string name="G67_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="G67_Ans2">Climbing rocks.</string> // leads to G78_Story

    <string name="G72_Story">While checking out the area with Greg, you see a glint of something larger that\'s metallic. You call Greg over and brush
        away the dirt from a small metallic chain... to discover an old, broken, pocket watch. Well, this can be added to the pile of things for
        geocaching at least! Other than that, nothing else of interest comes up, so it's time to continue exploring! Continue down the side tunnel, or
        keep following the tracks?</string>
    <string name="G72_Ans1">Explore the tunnel.</string> // leads to G79_Story
    <string name="G72_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to G84_Story

    <string name="G73_Story">Let\'s not waste time digging through dirt. Continue down the side tunnel, or keep following the tracks?</string>
    <string name="G73_Ans1">Explore the tunnel.</string> // leads to G79_Story
    <string name="G73_Ans2">Follow the tracks.</string> // leads to G84_Story

    <string name="G78_Story">As you work your way up, the climb takes about as much effort as a steep hike, and Greg helps pull you up to the top... a
        bit muddy if nothing else. As you continue on, there is a natural arch that overlooks the river where you can hear the water quickly rushing -
        how cool! But wait, what\'s that further on down? Another cave? Another dig site? It looks like someone set up a camp here, but decades ago.
        What catches your eye is another glint of something metallic, near a sack of some sort. Coins? Greg looks excited, but even he's stopped to
        check things out. He mentions that the river looks pretty wild here, and points to where it is focused into a fast-moving spot. Do you want to
        brave it and go check out the camp site? Or turn back because it could be really dangerous this time?</string>
    <string name="G78_Ans1">Get the shinies!</string> // leads to G85_Story
    <string name="G78_Ans2">Backtrack.</string> // leads to G90_Story

    <string name="G79_Story">Down the tunnel you go, and with Greg in tow! Greg absent-mindedly kicks a rock, which hits the wall with a *clunk* and
        seems to dislodge a few more. You give him a bit of a scowl as he grins sheepishly at you, and mumbles out a \"Whoops! Sorry.\" as you continue
        on down the tracks. A few more creaks and groans from the tunnel beams quickens your pace a bit, and you hope nothing shifted too much.</string>
    <string name="G79_Ans1"></string> // this button will be hidden
    <string name="G79_Ans2">Continue.</string> // leads to G91_Story

    <string name="G84_Story">You make your way in what appears to be a junction of some sort. The tracks continue down the tunnel, but now there is
        another set that lead away down the left. In the middle is a circular contraption that looks like was used to change the direction of a mine
        cart. All around here are various discarded tools used for mining. You notice an old pickaxe, a rusty lantern, and a shovel; all of which are
        haphazardly lying about in various states of disrepair. An old minecart is toppled over off to the side, and some sort of noise is coming from
        it. Greg grabs the rusty lantern and throws it at the mine cart. A big brown rat squeaks and bolts out from under it, quickly making its way
        down the tunnels. Greg chuckles as you give him a smirk. Do you search around, or keep going?</string>
    <string name="G84_Ans1">Search the cart.</string> // leads to G96_Story
    <string name="G84_Ans2">Move on.</string> // leads to G97_Story

    <string name="G85_Story">You look around for a way down, and manage to find a rocky area that seems to have enough hand and foot holds to get down
        to the river. As you start to climb down, the rocks come out from your grasp! OH NO! *SPLASH!* You fall into the river and briefly try to orient
        yourself before hitting your head on something that hurts! ...as all goes black... ... ... ...you wake up spluttering and disoriented with Greg
        laughing frantically, mentioning he jumped in after you and brought you back to the edge. Fortunately he knew CPR, otherwise you might\'ve been
        a goner! Your head is pounding, and slightly bloody, but at least you\'re alive - too bad adventure time is over. Greg helps you up, and you
        start an agonizing trip back home.</string>
    <string name="G85_Ans1">Try again!</string> // leads to T1_Story
    <string name="G85_Ans2">Play later.</string> // leads to End_Story

    <string name="G90_Story">Backtracking</string>
    <string name="G90_Ans1"></string> // leads to G102_Story
    <string name="G90_Ans2"></string> // leads to G103_Story

    <string name="G91_Story">While making your way further down the tunnel, you start to hear a faint *whooshing* noise coming from further ahead. A
        squishy, gurgly, grumbly noise emanates from your stomach, and then Greg\'s, and you both realise that it\'s been a bit before you had
        something to eat. Fortunately you remembered to at least grab an energy bar before heading out! Unfortunately it\'s not enough to feed the both
        of you, as Greg gives you a starving dog look. With a resigned sigh, you split the bar in half and give him some, which he gobbles down quickly.
        You\'re not sure if he actually ate it, or just swallowed it whole. Shaking your head a bit, you take a drink from your water bottle, and hand
        it over to Greg who drinks the rest. Wherever we are going, we need to be quick about it!</string>
    <string name="G91_Ans1"></string> // leads to G108_Story
    <string name="G91_Ans2"></string> // leads to G109_Story

    <string name="G96_Story">You search around the area, but don\'t find anything of interest. Greg checks out where the rat was and finds a nest of
        some sort, full of various bits of grasses, string, pieces of paper, and other innocuous things. With a sigh, he looks over at you and asks
        where to next?</string>
    <string name="G96_Ans1">Follow left tunnel.</string> // leads to G114_Story
    <string name="G96_Ans2">Continue straight.</string> // leads to G115_Story

    <string name="G97_Story">You decide you don\'t want to know why a large rat found that cart appealing. A new tunnel branches off to the left, or
        you can continue straight.</string>
    <string name="G97_Ans1">Follow left tunnel.</string> // leads to G114_Story
    <string name="G97_Ans2">Continue straight.</string> // leads to G115_Story

    <string name="G102_Story">backtracking</string>
    <string name="G102_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G102_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G103_Story">backtracking</string>
    <string name="G103_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G103_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G108_Story">Hoping Greg doesn\'t resort to cannibalism</string>
    <string name="G108_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G108_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G109_Story">Hoping Greg doesn\'t resort to cannibalism</string>
    <string name="G109_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G109_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G114_Story">following left tunnel</string>
    <string name="G114_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G114_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G115_Story">continuing straight</string>
    <string name="G115_Ans1"></string> // leads to G
    <string name="G115_Ans2"></string> // leads to G

    <string name="G120_Story"></string>
    <string name="G120_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="G120_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="G121_Story"></string>
    <string name="G121_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="G121_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="G126_Story"></string>
    <string name="G126_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="G126_Ans2"></string>

    <string name="G127_Story"></string>
    <string name="G127_Ans1"></string>
    <string name="G127_Ans2"></string>

</resources>
